

Kevin SmeraglioFull Stack Web Developer

33 E 8th Ave • Conshohocken, PA 215-499-6566 • ksmera01@gmail.com

PROFILE

Full Stack Web Developer with experience as a Business Systems Manager in the information technology field. Earned a certificate in Full Stack Web Development from the University of Pennsylvania LPS Coding Boot Camp where I honed skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js and React.js. Recognized as a team player and hard worker, my focus is on meeting deadlines and getting the job done. In addition, I have managed developers giving me a unique perspective on scope and project management systems such as JIRA. I am excited to use my creativity, passion and skills to build meaningful web applications!

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Systems Manager

Physician Recommended Nutriceuticals and Veterinarian Recommended Solutions (February 2016 – Present)

- Maintenance and optimization of NetSuite, ERP and CRM system
- Coaching and mentoring on the functionality, applicability, and usability to all users of NetSuite, Google Apps and Contivio.
- Atlassian JIRA Software and JIRA Service Desk
- Elicit, capture, analyze, and document business and user requirements.
- Provide support of existing reporting applications and handle all aspects of design, construction and development of new reporting solutions.
- Verify testing output to ensure it meets the requirements of the business requirements.
- Manage relationships with outside developers, vendors, and partners on daily basis.

Business Systems and Support Specialist

Physician Recommended Nutriceuticals

(June 2015 – February 2016)

- Provide Desktop and Laptop end user support
- Manage applications including Microsoft Office, WebEx, Call Center Phone System
- Google Apps Admin
- NetSuite Admin
- Asset Management
- New User Setup
- Identify opportunities to improve current processes and to act as a champion to change within the enterprise applications
- Write technical documents and procedures when necessary for staff

Quality Assurance Analyst

Opvantek, Inc.

(May 2012 - April 2015)

- Work to maintain the desired level of quality for the company's main products including Optimain DS (Decision Support), ACM (Asset Compliance Management), and xDR (Damage Risk).
- Create and run test cases and defects.

• Work with SmallWorld and other GIS applications on a daily basis.

EDUCATION

UPenn LPS Coding Bootcamp

Feb 2020 – August 2020

Philadelphia, PA *Certificate*

Related Coursework/Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- Express.js

- React.js
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- MySQL
- Command Line
- Git

Gwynedd Mercy University

Gwynedd Valley, PA

2008 - 2012

Bachelor of Science (BS), Business Administration and Management Colonial States Athletic Conference (CSAC) All-Academic Team, Deans List

NCAA Student Athlete

Holy Ghost Preparatory School

Bensalem, PA

2004-2008

Academic Diploma National Art Honors Society